I say, it's time for "Supercharged."
现在是增压的时候了。
My name is Paul.
我叫保罗。
And I'm here to help, you know?
我在这里帮助您，您知道吗？
Mhm, yes.
欢迎来到增压。
I'm Paul.
我是保罗
This is the show where you submit your sites,
这是您提交网站的地方，
I go through them, and I try to find the performance problems
我浏览它以查找性能问题
and recommend some fixes.
我会建议一些解决方案。
Now, today, I've got "The Guardian."
今天我们有“高卢人”。
I have spoken with them before, and I
我以前跟他们说过话，我知道
know they actually do a really good job with things
他们擅长制作诸如纹理之类的东西。
But we're going to run it through Webpage Test anyway,
但是我们还是要通过网页扫描来运行它，
first view only.
只有首场演出
I'm going to run it on mobile 3G with a Nexus 5.0 this time,
这次，我将在Nexus 5.0和Chrome上使用3G浏览。
It's like watching paint dry.
就像看着油漆变干一样。
Welcome to "Supercharged."
欢迎来到“增压”。
I say, this test is taking rather a long time.
这项检查需要很长时间。
Making people wait their turn.
它使人们等待轮到他们。
Do you know who I am?
你知道我是谁吗
You'll prioritize me if you know what's good for you.
如果您知道自己有什么好处，请优先考虑。
So we've got the web page test result, which looks good.
我们有网页扫描结果，很好。
And I tell you what we'll do.
我会告诉你我们将做什么？
We'll dive into the filmstrip view
我们将深入电影胶片
because that's always good fun.
而且总是很有趣。
I noticed that the speed index was about 6,700.
我注意到速度指示器约为6700
And so I would expect something for, like, the gold standard
因此，我期望例如黄金标准
to be somewhere around the 3,000 mark.
在3,000的郊区。
I mean, give or take.
当然了
Now, as I scroll to the left, we're
现在，我向左拖动
sort of a blank white screen for about 4 and 1/2 seconds.
我们将在4秒半的时间内看到空白页。
And then at five seconds, we're actually
然后五秒钟
starting to see page content.
我们将开始查看页面的内容。
Now, because if we look at the bottom,
现在，如果我们看一下底部，
we can see that there's still the HTML.
我们将看到HTML仍在加载。
And that's coming in.
这来了。
And as we get to the end of that,
到最后，
we actually start to see render.
我们实际上将开始观看演示。
So that means they are inlining styles.
这意味着他们正在协调模式，
Because the only way we could get to the end of the HTML
因为只有这样才能引导我们结束HTML
and start rendering is if there's some inline styles.
开始显示的是存在协调的模式。
So that's a really good thing.
这是一件非常好的事情。
Print css?
要打印CSS文件？
I'm on a phone.
我在打电话。
I don't expect to print.
我不希望打印。
It's a minor thing.
这是一件小事。
It is extremely minor because it's only 2.9K.
它很小，因为它的容量仅为2.9 KB。
But it is a connection that we're making.
但这是我们创建的连接。
And I wonder whether that needs to be made.
我想知道是否需要这样做。
But that's throw away.
但这并不重要。
I wouldn't even worry about it.
我不用担心
You know, unless you're worried about it.
你知道，如果你担心的话
If you're worried about it, do something.
如果是的话，为此做点什么。
But don't-- I'm not saying you should worry.
但是不，我并不是说你应该。
I'm not worried.
我不担心
That HTML does look quite large.
该HTML看起来很棒。
It's 83K.
它的容量为83 KB。
83K, you know, that will be gzipped as well.
83 kb，将进行“压缩”压缩。
So that's a fair amount to be sending down
这是一个合理的下载量
as the initial burst of content.
基于第一批内容。
I wonder whether it would be better
如果是最好的
to actually send down less HTML and then
我们下载的HTML更少
use Ajax to pull things in.
然后，我们使用Ajax将事物引入。
That might just boost things a tiny amount.
这可能会加快速度。
Let's actually have a look at the HTML Itself.
让我们看一下HTML本身。
Hey!
欢迎光临
They're hiring too.
他们也雇用。
Bit of an advert in there.
这里的简短公告。
Busted that wide open for you.
我为你传播。
This looks like our inline styles here.
这些看起来像格式化的样式。
OK, let's grab some of that.
让我们来一些。
Because I am curious as to how much of inline styling
我对定型观念的数量感到好奇
we are seeing-ing-ing.
我们看到了。
I'm going to try that again in English.
我会用英语再试一次。
I'm wondering how much inline styles we're actually seeing.
我想知道我们有多少定型观念。
So let me grab all this.
让我接受所有这些。
It keeps on going.
它继续出现。
Going to copy that.
我会复制这个。
What I'm going to do is I'm going to fire up Sublime.
我要做的是打开Sublime。
And I'm going to paste it in.
并粘贴到里面。
Let's save that on our desktop as like, file.css.
让我们将其保存在桌面上
OK.
我们打开了车站。
So what we'll do is we will go to my desktop where I saved
我们要做的就是转到我的桌面
And it is 179K of inline styles.
我们有179 KB的坐标模式。
But that's not fair because what we should do
这不公平，因为我们必须做
is we should gzip file.css.
File.css以gzip方式压缩。
This is all finger-in-the-air kind of stuff.
这是每个人都应该做的事情之一。
And let's see what we get.
让我们看看会出现什么。
So ls - lah, and then we'll just tab that up.
我们将通过按Tab重写ls -lah。
And we'll go.
现在是22 KB。
So that's still quite small.
所以它仍然很小。
But if you want to get something inside the initial response
如果要从服务器的“第一响应”中获取某些信息
from a server, it's got to be in the first, I think, 14K or so
它必须是第一个，我认为应该是大约14 KB
to account for TCP slow start and all that good stuff.
为了弥补TCP等缓慢的问题。
So this is probably quite a large amount of inline styles.
可能是大量的协调模式
But we have one other trick up our sleeves
但是我们还有另一招
here, which I will show you.
我会告诉你的。
Now, the credit for this goes to Matt Gaunt,
而现在，感谢Matt Gunt。
one of my colleagues.
我的一位同事。
He came up with this.
他发现了。
And it's based off the Filament Group's loadcss library.
它基于Filament集合loadcss库。
What I've got here is a bookmarklet
我这里有一个信号
which, when I click it, is going to switch off any styles that
当我单击它时，它将禁用任何模式
have been loaded in remotely and just leave the inline styles.
远程上传，仅保留格式样式。
What it does is it goes through the stylesheets.
她要做的就是看样式表。
And it switches off the remote styles
它禁用远程样式
by just giving them a media type that is rubbish.
通过给他们无效的模式。
And it goes, well, these don't apply anymore.
因此，它们不开放。
A ridge.
山顶。
Let's just put it on the ridge.
让我们把它们放在最上面。
So this is what it looks like when
那就是它所显示的
there are no remote styles, just the inline styles applied.
如果没有尺寸模式，则只有格式设置模式。
(WITH FUNNY ACCENT) Sonny, in the United Kingdom,
英国天晴，
what is this?
这是什么
Global warming, you see, climate change.
原因是全球变暖，气候变化。
it feels like the inline styles that have been applied
就像应用了格式化模式
don't set the layout up.
不要调整页面布局。
Now, it could be that there's some other work that's
可能已完成一些工作
gone on with the JavaScript to change things around.
通过JavaScript改变事物。
But as a first pass, I would be looking at this going, hmm.
乍一看，我会看到这一点，我很纳闷。
When I switch off the remote styles,
当我禁用邮政模式时，
I want the inline styles to be color blocks and layouts
我希望格式样式为颜色块和布局
and stuff so that we stop things moving around.
这将阻止事物四处移动。
But mainly, so that we can get something up on screen.
但基本上是使事物出现在屏幕上。
The whole point of the inline css
CSS协调的目标
is, hopefully, to just kind of bootstrap up
有点启动
that initial viewport and get us going.
到首映，使我们继续前进。
So much for the page load, then, which
就像加载页面一样，
is actually really looking good.
实际上看起来很棒。
I think there are some tweaks that they could potentially
我认为这是他们可以做的一些改进
make to crush down the inline styles
实施它们以减少初始格式
and, you know, not put so much in there,
所以你知道，不要在那儿放太多
and put what is really important in there,
他们只把重要的东西
not just what seems important.
似乎并不重要。
What we'll do next time is we'll actually
下次我们会做什么
dive into the performance characteristics of things
是要深入研究表演事物的特征
like this, scrolling and so on.
喜欢搬家等等。
So stick around for that.
因此，请继续关注。
And I'll see you next time.
下次见。
I'm the only on camera and the only one
我是镜头前唯一的一个
they let on camera these days.
这些天唯一允许这样做的人。
Take two.
第二枪。
Or as I like to call it, the professional cut.
我喜欢称之为专业叙事。
I think there's a point on the top of my head.
我认为我的头顶上方有一点。
Paul Lewis, man boy.
保罗·刘易斯，孩子。